[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "We followed the evidence.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", ":"], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Bill Nye, your response?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Well, we start talking about the facts, those --", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bill Nye"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "Do you agree that when I was a kid or when you were a kid, there was 340 parts per million of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", ",", "EX", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "What's your point?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "And what do you put that rate down to, Bill?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "TO", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "It's human activity.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["2.999 billion"]}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "CD", "TO", "CD", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 76, "question": "And what are the biggest factors, the manmade factors creating the acceleration of CO2 in the atmosphere?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 77, "answer": "Well, the biggest thing is when I was 9 years old, the earth's population changed from 2.999 billion to three billion.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "How do you explain that the Eastern Seaboard, for example, is getting some of the warmest weather it's ever had at the same time that California has been plunged into storm after storm in the last week and you see New York last month had the worst hurricane it's ever endured and so on and so on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Eastern Seaboard", "California", "New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "How do you explain that we're getting so many of these freakish weather patterns if at the same time you've got all this extra CO2 in the atmosphere and all these people now guzzling up power and energy and emitting gases that weren't there before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "RP", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Surely that is evidence, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "What was your take on the two meetings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Well, we were honored to be invited.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Don't you feel like you're batting the wrong kind of game here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Well, that's for the Congress to decide and that's part of the debate.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "Why wasn't this done in the first quarter?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Well, Piers, as you know, there were a number of efforts before the election to get this done and there were major differences between the parties, and those parties became a big part of the conversation during the presidential debate.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["first quarter"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "VBN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", ",", "CC", "RB", "TO", "VB", "CD", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WDT", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CD", "JJ", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "What is the way through this and how is this likely, in your expert opinion, to be resolved?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "Well, first of all, I think it took the very tough two closings of the federal government, one for six days, the other for 21 days, in order to get to a point where we were able to negotiate seriously to get welfare reform, which was vetoed twice and then signed, and then to get four consecutive balanced budgets, which was a pretty substantial accomplishment, the only time in your lifetime we've had four consecutive American balanced budgets.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "Are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "Well, Piers, I'm happy for you to pay it, too.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Would you be happy to?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Of course I'm prepared.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 432, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 433, "answer": "Feel good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 435, "question": "How many people do you meet on a daily basis who go, you are my hero?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 436, "answer": "A lot of people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "When you get down on those blocks and you are about to explode, what actually goes through the Golden Bolt's mind?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "TO", "VB", ",", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "All you try to do is just relax, really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 456, "question": "Not just any old champion, to be a great champion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 457, "answer": "Well, it's just hard work.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 475, "question": "Is it all of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 476, "answer": "It's everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 496, "question": "Is there something in the Jamaican yam?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 497, "answer": "I think it may have something to do with yams.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Johnson"]}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "Sporting heroes?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "For me, Michael Johnson was definitely one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 510, "question": "What about other sports?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 511, "answer": "Other sports.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 529, "question": "Can you do the Gangnam?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 530, "answer": "I can do a little bit.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Your thoughts?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "I remember at the Olympics --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Beijing"]}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 546, "question": "Coming from him, he hasn't exactly got the most graceful style, has he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 547, "answer": "I remember at the Olympics, the first Olympics in Beijing, I remember when I was going to run the 200 meters.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "You got no game?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "CD", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "``", "CD", "NN", ",", "CD", "NN", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", "RB", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 589, "question": "Can you do any Bob Marley for me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "My one song I always sing is like, \"one love, one heart, let's get together and feel all right.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bob Marley"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Why would I be bitter about that, you say?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "I don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "The cue?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "The line, whatever you call it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 631, "question": "Is this true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 632, "answer": "No, I'm single right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 633, "question": "You're single?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 634, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "What can I say man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "Let's talk Rio.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 641, "question": "Are you going to go for it in Rio?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 642, "answer": "Without a doubt.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 643, "question": "How many -- as you sit here now, how many do you think you can race in Rio?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 644, "answer": "Well, I've mentioned this to my coach and I have said it to him.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 655, "question": "These are Puma, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 656, "answer": "They're light for the size.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Puma"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 658, "question": "You wear these?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 659, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2002"]}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNS", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "Usain, there's a question I always ask people, if you had five minutes to live and I had the power to relive a moment for you from your life, what would you choose?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "World Juniors 2002.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Why that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "It was one of my -- it was a life changing experience for me in every sense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 677, "question": "Once?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 678, "answer": "I had a girl friend for seven years.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 679, "question": "Did she break your heart?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "Vice versa.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]